Just... Just one thing.
We're in a great place right now.
l don't wanna do anything
that will make stuff weird again.
- So we won't let it get weird.
- Okay.
Oh, just a heads up. Mm.
Since the last time you saw me naked...
...l got a Cookie Monster tattoo.
(Penny:)The acceptable responses when you
see it are "awesome" or nothing.
(Leonard:)What about...
(Leonard:)...cookies.
Amy. Amy. Amy
(Amy:)Seven o'clock. Right on time.
(Sheldon:)It's not an accident.
l waited outside your door
for 20 minutes.
(Amy:)Well, dinner's almost ready.
l must say I was surprised you chose to
spend our date-night in your apartment.
Well, as I mentioned, uh...
(Sheldon:)...the Pasadena City Council
is debating longer crosswalk times...
(Sheldon:)...and later, the Lego store
is having a Midnight Madness sale.